{
  "questionList": {
    "question1": [
      {
        "id":1,
        "answer": "Rowan Atkinson",
        "question": "Who played Mr.Bean character?",
        "option1": "William Charle",
        "option2": "Rowan Atkinson",
        "option3":"William Atkinson"
      },
      {
            "id":2,
        "answer": "Gene Deitch",
        "question": "Who is the creator for Tom & Jerry?",
        "option1": "Gene Deitch",
        "option2": "John Williams",
        "option3":"Steven James"
      },
      {
            "id":3,
        "answer": "23",
        "question": "How many years of uninterrupted Run was completed For DDLJ Movie in Maratha Mandir,Mumbai?",
        "option1": "23",
        "option2": "25",
        "option3":"24"
      },
      {
            "id":4,
        "answer": "Best Actor",
        "question": "Joaquin Phoenix was awarded for Which category in Academy Awards?",
        "option1": "Best Actor",
        "option2": "Best Director",
        "option3":"Best Writer"
      },
      {
        "id":5,
        "answer": "A.R.Rahman",
        "question": "Who composed music for SlumDog Millionaire?",
        "option1": "A.R.Rahman",
        "option2": "Chris Dickens",
        "option3":"Jameson"
      },
      {
            "id":6,
        "answer": "India",
        "question": "A.R.Rahman is from which country?",
        "option1": "Srilanka",
        "option2": "India",
        "option3":"Nepal"
      },
      
      {
            "id":7,
        "answer": "Spain",
        "question": "In which Country the largest movie theatere in the world was located?",
        "option1": "Spain",
        "option2": "France",
        "option3":"Italy"
      },
      {
        "id":8,
        "answer": "Avengers:EndGame",
        "question": "World Best Movie in 2019 is?",
        "option1": "Parasite",
        "option2": "Avengers:EndGame",
        "option3":"Spiderman"
      },
      {
            "id":9,
        "answer": "Walt Disney",
        "question": "Who is the producer of Avengers:EndGame?",
        "option1": "Walt Disney",
        "option2": "Fox Entertainments",
        "option3":"Sony"
      },
      {
            "id":10,
        "answer": "American Film Studio",
        "question": "Walt Disney studios is an?",
        "option1": "American Film Studio",
        "option2": "British Film Studio",
        "option3" : "German Film Studio"
      },
      {
            "id":11,
        "answer": "Leonardo Dicaprio",
        "question": "Who acted in Titanic as Jack?",
        "option1": "Leonardo Dicaprio",
        "option2": "Billy Zane",
        "option3":"Moore"
      },
      {
            "id":12,
        "answer": "Rose",
        "question": "Which character was played by Kate Winslet in Titanic Film?",
        "option3": "Rose",
        "option1":"Tulip",
        "option2": "Lilly"
      },
      {
            "id":13,
        "answer": "James Cameron",
        "question": "Who Directed the Titanic Film?",
        "option1": "James Cameron",
        "option2": "Terence Davies",
        "option3":"Danny Cannon"
      },
      {
        "id":14,
        "answer": "1997",
        "question": "In which year Titanic Movie was Released?",
        "option1": "1997",
        "option2": "1998",
        "option3":"1996"
      },
      {
        "id":15,
        "answer": "7",
        "question": "How many series of Harry Potter books were published?",
        "option1": "8",
        "option2": "7",
        "option3":"6"
      },
      {
        "id":16,
        "answer": "J.K.Rowling",
        "question": "Who is the Author of Harry Potter?",
        "option1": "J.K.Rowling",
        "option2": "Chris Columbus",
        "option3":"Basil Dean"
      },
      {
        "id":17,
        "answer": "Railway",
        "question": "Which Harry Potter Bridge was located in Scotland?",
        "option1": "Railway",
        "option2": "Millenium",
        "option3":"Heaven Bridge"
      },
      {
        "id":18,
        "answer": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "The Philiosopher's Stone book was belongs to which series?",
        "option1": "Harry Potter",
        "option2": "parasite",
        "option3":"Avatar"
      },
      {
        "id":19,
        "answer": "Reginald Dwight",
        "question": "What is Elton John's real name?",
        "option1": "Reginald Dwight",
        "option2": "Regiland Dwighet",
        "option3": "Bill Douglas"
      },
      {
        "id":20,
        "answer": "52",
        "question": "How many awards has Andrew Lloyd Webber won in his carrer",
        "option1": "57",
        "option2": "52"
      }
    ]
  }
}
